This is Trigun.
Oh, my God.
That's right, he's the man with the
60 billion double dollars on his head.
They say he showed up in Dankentown
recently, made quite a mess, I hear.
Heh, so what happened?
The whole town got zapped.
Mountains of corpses all over Dankin.
The coffin maker got so rich, he
built himself a mansion of wood.
Guy sounds plain crazy.
He's more than crazy.
I think we'd be wise to
keep a safe distance.
Messing with Vash is
like dancing with death.
He leaves a trail of
destruction wherever he goes.
Women, children, he don't care.
He'll kill them all.
They call him the humanoid typhoon.
I don't
know.
I finally found you.
One night.
And just look at this place.
I didn't believe the rumors, but
this guy really is a typhoon.
Over half the town ain't
nothing but rubble now.
That's real shame, but the
Undertakers must be happy.
So how many did he get this time?
One hundred? Two hundred?
Actually, zero.
There's a whole lot of injuries,
but somehow no fatalities at all.
I guess we had a miracle here.
Without God's help.
So what was he like?
Well, he wore red, had earrings,
a giant man with short legs.
I'm afraid I didn't get a
real good look at him myself.
Thanks, Sheriff.
Whatever you do, stay away from him.
For your own good. Red.
The area of Dankin is mostly demolished.
All residents go to your
designated shelter areas.
The next update will be 4.30 p .m.
Until then, please enjoy
our musical selection.
What do you have?
A banana sundae. Huh?
And I will have a Kaite
Milly foie with Ceylon tea.
Listen,
missus, I'm afraid you'd better order milk
with that or that gag ain't gonna work.
Yeah, cause if you did, we'd give you
all the milk you could possibly want.
Although I hate to tell you,
but it wouldn't exactly be free.
But I didn't say milk, I said Ceylon-T.
Hey!
Oh, sorry.
You little bitch, you!
Oh!
The student's leg broke again.
You have a spare, don't you?
You should be more careful.
Yeah, I know.
What the hell is she?
She's a monster.
By the way, mister, we heard that Vash the
Stampede showed up in Felgnarl recently.
Is there anything you can tell us?
What about Bash?
And why are you asking?
Don't tell me you two
innocent-looking things
are after that $60 billion
double-dollar reward.
Oh, not at all.
Yeah, actually, we're just
passing through here on business.
Business?
Well, I didn't exactly see him myself.
As far as I could tell, he was
gone from the city by dawn.
Last I heard, he was
headed out to the east.
Can you tell me any more about him?
Hmm well he stands about 12
fields tall and he wields
a huge weapon he's supposed
to have a mohawk and nerves
of steel apparently he's
got tons of henchmen and a
reputation is the worst
womanizer anyone's ever seen?
Womanizer I heard what he said huge
weapon and a mohawk that's our man all!
right.
Where is he?
Where the hell did he go?
I don't care if you
have to dig up the whole
area.
I want you to find him.
I don't believe it.
That little coward couldn't be him.
I don't
see any point sticking around this place.
Let's just move on.
So you think you're big enough to give
me orders now, you little weasel, huh?
You saw what he was wearing?
You know
I know that it's him.
Find him no matter what or I'll
have to break your neck, okay?
I thought I was going to
suffocate a minute there.
It's fast, boy!
Hi there! Pardon me.
Thanks for nothing, fellas.
That was a pretty close one.
I almost bought the farm back there.
It's actually a miracle that
I got away with it this time.
I found him!
Over there!
Perfect shot!
Well, he thinks he's funny.
Hunt him down. Right.
I'm getting hungry.
They're persistent.
Ha ha ha!
I'm like a sitting duck over here.
I'm defenseless.
Oh, shit.
Now, stand real still.
You wouldn't want this
gun to go off, would you?
I found him.
He's right over here boss.
Uh, would you mind lowering
your gun like a good boy?
Forget it You don't like pain, do you?
I'm used to it. Well,
I feel sorry for your wife
and kids You'll make them cry
ain't got no kids and most
women find me pretty offensive.
So I'm single sounds
like a pretty lonely life
I'm telling you.
You have to die!
It would sure make us all happy if you do!
Sorry, I don't do requests.
Get down!
Boss!
Help me!
That's good work. My compliments.
Attacking while your pal
is in the line of fire.
Don't you care about him at all?
We're not pals.
Our fate is our being partners.
The only possible way he can
be happy is when I'm happy.
That's just beautiful.
You can shoot me if that'd
make you feel better.
That is, if your big gun of
yours isn't just for show.
Actually, I can't stand blood.
Just the very side of it
makes me feel a little faint.
Fine, then.
How about we find out what happens when
you get to see your own blood, huh?
Now, it would make me real
happy if you go hold him down.
There, now.
Do you see how devoted he is?
Hey, couldn't you guys be
just a little bit more gentle?
Alright, let's get our precious
little cargo to the feds right away.
Yeah, we're gonna be filthy rich!
Women?
Are they friends of his?
Well, are they gonna try
and steal our reward?
We're going in.
Right.
Now what do you want?
I'm very pleased to meet you.
My name is Meryl.
I'm Meryl Stryfe and I'm here representing
the Bernardelli Insurance Society.
And I'm Millie Thompson.
This is a small token of our goodwill.
Nice going, Meryl!
What are you doing?
Are you here with him?
Actually, not at all.
We were sent here by the Bernardelli
Insurance Society to investigate a report of -
I finally found you.
It's the 60 billion double
dollar big bounty. Mr.
Vash the Stampede. Huh?
Huh? Huh?
My name is Luce Ruth,
I'm a bounty hunter, and some
people know me as Constance Rifle.
Mr.
Vash the Stampede, time you know that
I'm here for the price on your head.
What's that?
Well, Merrill?
This looks bad.
Uh, did I miss something?
Mr.
Vash the Stampede, it's
a privilege to meet you.
Your face is starting to look like
it belongs on the double dollar.
You really can't blame me
for coming after you now,
since your head is worth 60 billion.
What do we do, Meryl?
I think it's pretty obvious.
We've gotta... stop them.
So, did you say your name was Ruth?
Uh, could you excuse me?
Well, I'm glad to see
you enjoy your work, Mr.
Ruth, but I'm afraid that
you're just a little bit late.
Please, listen to me! Me, late?
I don't reckon so.
You asshole!
What the hell do you
think you're aiming at?
Just a sixty billion double
dollar skull, that's all.
Don't be a moron!
You think the boss is Vash?
Where the hell did you get that idea?
I ain't fool enough to
listen to some lame henchman.
Sorry, joke's over and I ain't laughing.
Huh, this is just stupid.
Quit wasting my time.
Get the hell out of it!
Don't move.
You're dressed in a red coat, you've
got earrings, and your legs are short.
I'm convinced you are Vash the Stampede.
You're out of your mind!
Vash is a blond-haired man in a red coat,
and he carries a great big handgun, okay?
No, he isn't.
Vash the Stampede is a giant man with
a really huge weapon and a mohawk!
That's awfully strange.
Yeah, the rumors don't match.
So what do we do now?
What do we do now?
We have no choice but to
believe what we've heard.
But Meryl...
You're all crazy!
I'm not Vash! Hey, boss! Look!
The Fenzel pays 60 billion double dollars
for Vash the Stampede, dead or alive.
So it's your choice, friend.
I'd be happy to kill you now, if you like.
So he's blonde.
Has a red coat, a big gun.
I get it.
You're trying to get the
jump on me, aren't you?
Vash the Stampede! What'd he say?
You even came up with
that stupid fake name!
Nice touch!
Wait a minute.
He is definitely the real thing.
Let's get him!
Hmm. Well, I'll be.
So this is how he stayed alive this long.
Come on, shoot!
You bastard!
Don't push your luck!
I'm really scared.
The Humanoid typeset is on the loose.
What do we do, Meryl?
What do we do? Duh.
We run away, that's what.
I guess it is important
to stay alive, isn't it?
We'll have to get the town the
evacuation order immediately.
But Meryl, isn't running away like this
the same as if we were abandoning our post?
It's more important that
we contact the town now.
Mmm, these are really good!
When did you get here?
Thanks a lot!
I'm really getting hungry!
These donuts hit the spot!
Give me those!
You know, we didn't come out here
just to save your sorry butt!
Okay, then, what were you two doing there?
Are ugly donuts like that?
You're tight for what?
Shut up!
It's not like that at all!
We came to this place
on official business!
That's right!
Official representatives of the
Bernard Daly Insurance Society!
We're disaster investigators!
So, if you're really insurance people,
Why are you so interested
in such a dangerous bounty?
There's been over 300 incidents
involving Bash the Stampede.
It's a huge liability for
any insurance company.
Gotta understand risks.
Insurance company takes.
Yeah, that must be rough.
Like you care.
That's why we have to
find Bash the Stampede
and keep him under 24 hours surveillance.
It's the only way to
prevent further damage.
24 hours?
Is something wrong? No, nothing.
Oh, I got it.
Alright, I'm prepared to make you a deal
in exchange for this and the doughnuts!
Would you consider going into
town and warning the people?
I'll even lend you my own personal Thomas.
Are you actually going back there?
It's the job.
It's what I do
Looks like it's all over.
Good, there don't seem
to be any casualties?
But Meryl, didn't that
bounty hunter get killed?
I'd call that a casualty.
That's true. It's very sad.
Well, how are we going to
approach him this time?
Have you got some kind of plan?
Yeah, the deluxe box of 30.
Hey, what a great idea!
As long as we're clever about this and
treat them with courtesy and respect,
we have nothing to fear.
You've got a lot of
nerve coming back here.
Please accept this token of goodwill.
I hate prisons.
Now, where's the guy you ran away with?
Uh, I don't know.
We split up halfway.
And it was so damn hard to track him down.
What the hell are we
gonna do about this, Ruth?
You're alive?
How can you still be alive?
I thought you two were
fighting to the death.
It looks as though we
both made a little error.
We made the error?
In my opinion, you're the one
that screwed up, it wasn't me.
Listen here.
We're gonna split it.
70-30.
And don't you forget it.
What is all this about?
Time to go.
Hold on just a minute.
Oh, Meryl.
I guess I never should have
taken this job after all.
What good will this do?
These two are useless.
Don't worry about it.
Just enjoy them.
Oh, you've got bad taste.
Sick and twisted, but
actually I kind of like it.
They did say he was the
worst kind of womanizer.
Now is not the time to remind me of that.
I want to know what you prefer, ladies.
Pleasure before death, or
just death without pleasure?
Boss, we've got a big
problem! I'm busy! Yeah!
But actually, it's me with
the big roll over here!
Hit him back!
Got you!
Run!
I'm all looking for you!
That's the stampede!
Huh?
Where'd he go?
Where are you going?
To the potty, sir!
He did save our lives!
All right. Hold
it
right there.
Well, Vash, it's time to
choose your way to die.
Buy a boomerang or do a
suicide dive off a cliff.
Suicide?
To tell you the truth, I disapprove
of suicide more than anything.
Alright, the boomerang it is! No!
No!
Dangerous toys are fun,
but you couldn't get hurt!
He got the boss!
That guy isn't human!
What fragile bonds of loyalty.
Now you there!
You better look out!
What the hell?
It's just a little too late.
Well, friends, I really
hope you feel better.
That's amazing.
They actually got both of
them in a matter of minutes.
It's as if he were Vash the Stampede, huh?
Well, did I work off the donuts
and the ten double dollars?
Uh-huh.
You can't be him.
There's just no way.
Disaster report.
We have determined that the landslide
which destroyed Fel Noro was a
direct result of the illegal use of
explosives by a man called Loose Ruth.
Please pay all insurance
claims as per regulations.
After all that work, we're at
less than zero on our Vash hunt.
But we can't just ignore the rumors.
This is going to be difficult.
What about that crazy guy?
Hmm?
He couldn't possibly be Vash.
I just don't buy that.
Are you sure?
Vash the Stampede?
Yep, that's the one.
The man with 60 billion
double dollars on his head.
They say he showed up in Felnar.
Didn't you hear about it?
Nope, so what happened?
Funny thing is, they say nobody died.
You mean like you don't
need God for a miracle?
Let's go.
But I'll just leave my eyes
I'll just leave my eyes
With my
eyes and eyes
I'll just
leave my eyes
I'll see you
next time.
There's something that
cannot be expressed in words.
Human emotion.
Emotions of the heart can't
just be tucked away in a closet.
There's a way to know the emotions.
Look into the eyes.
The girl lied to me.
And I believed her.
The gentleman lied to me.
When I trusted him.
But the moment I looked into his eyes,
the angel of destiny began
to unravel the truth.
Just looking at their eyes,
there is only one truth.